ELIZABETH WELCH

OBJECTIVE

A background in web design coupled with training in web development and computer programming makes me a great asset to any team requiring a programmer with an eye for user experience. I am comfortable working in C#, C++ and VB.NET, and have created mobile first web applications using ASP.NET MVC. Ideally, my work would allow me to utilize and expand upon my knowlede of one or many of these languages.

SKILLS

Programming:

- HTML, CSS, PHP, some JavaScript, Java, good understanding of Bootstrap
- C#, C++, VB.NET
- Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio
- ASP.NET MVC

Design:

- Adobe Creative Suite inc.:
 - Illustrator
 - Photoshop
 - InDesign

Other:

- Capable of organizing groups of people by assigning tasks that focus on strengths while minimizing weaknesses
- Organized and self-motivated worker

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer

Durham College, April 2018 Two Year Diploma, Dean's List

B.A., Graphic Design

Portland State University, December 2013 Earned with a focus on Web Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Database Developer

Durham College ORSIE

January 2, 2018-August 31, 2018

Created database architecture using Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio to serve as the new home of a company's existing 20+ years of recorded data, with the goal of improving report generation speed and allowing for future database, and company, growth.

Web Development and UX Research Assistant

Durham College ORSIE January 2018-April 2018

Worked with one other student to create a MVC based product website. Focused mostly on front-end coding and user experience, with some back-end tied in.

Web Development and UX Research Assistant

Durham College ORSIE February 2017-July 2017

Two separate projects:

Assisted another student in the development of an android application for a company focused on urban mobility. Created the landing page for a startup focused on greenhouse and farm inventory and sales.

Freelance Illustration

Freelance/Self-employed
February 2015-July 2016
Created illustrations and designs for clients.

Food Service Supervisor

Cascadia Market at Oregon State University

April-June, 2014 & September, 2014-January, 2015

Kept sales floor organized, created sales displays, directed & kept workers on task, assisted customers.

VOLUNTEER/OTHER EXPERIENCE

Friendtorship

October 2013-December 2013

Portland State University

Worked with high schoolers from Centennial Park School to make art and help nurture creativity.

Organized and ran workshops with the students.